Guide to the Daisy Aldan Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- June 2005 Acquisition, circa 1940-1980; Series XX; 1.63; (3 boxes)
  Fomer call number: Uncat MSS 779.
  Arranged by material type.
  Contains correspondence, writings, artwork, printed material, photographs and personal papers.
  Purchased from Charles Apfelbaum on the Elizabeth Wakeman Dwight Memorial Fund, 2005.
  Box 115: Restricted fragile material. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
  Box 116: Use of originals is restricted. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
  - Personal papers, 3 (Box 114)
  - Correspondence, 15 (Box 114)
  - Empty envelopes (Box 114)
  - "Breakthrough," typescript photocopy (Box 114)
  - "Of Arrows and Vectors," typescript photocopy (Box 114)
  - Poems (Box 114)
  - Printed material relating to Folder Editions, 7 (Box 114)
  - Newspaper clippings (Box 114)
  - Eurythmeum program (Box 114)
  - Artwork (Box 114)
  - Photographs, 5 (Box 114)
  - "Ella Heyde" sound recording (reel-to-reel tape) (Box 115)
  - "Mommy Am I Pretty?" and other songs sound recording (reel-to-reel tape) (Box 115)
  - Audiocassettes, 15 (Box 116)